HAILEY QUINN

186 Rocky Mountain Hwy, Unit 8, Denver, CO 56789 HaileyQuinn@icloud.com (564) 213'8763

Innovative medical scribe leader with 15 years of experience assisting physicians in clinical and hospital settings. Tech-savvy with new dictation software and electronic health records systems. Healthcare enthusiast focused on patient care and physician support.

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE IN BIOLOGY

University Of Colorado Boulder, CO 2002 - 2006

KEY SKILLS

- Staff Training & Development
- Medical Terminology & ICD-10
 Billing
- Patient History Documentation
- Health Information Systems
 Management
- Interpersonal Communications
- Collecting & Analyzing Vital Statistics
- EMR/EHR
- Medical Diagnosis Transcription& Data Entry
- Medical Team Leadership
- Chart Organization

CERTIFICATIONS

 CPR Training, American Red Cross, 2010

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

LEAD MEDICAL SCRIBE

CHI Urgent Family Care Clinic, Boulder, CO

November 2013 — Present

- Complete scheduling, audit transcribed notes, and field all calls regarding billing or insurance questions
- Oversee team of 15 tasked with assisting physicians, transcribing patient history and exams accurately, and processing billing with proper coding information and medical terminology
- Work with up to 100 patients daily ensuring they all have education for treatment, understanding of lest results, and information about any alternatives that may exist
- Ensure all physicians have chart and know reason for visit when speaking with patients prior to entering exam room

MEDICAL SCRIBE

Denver Family Physicians, Denver, CO September 2006 - October 2013

- Onboarded to aid up to 10 physicians within high-volume family practice.

 Worked with team of five other medical scribe professionals to ensure all medical providers had accurate documentation
- Viewed as subject matter expert on staff and provided training for new hires,
 interns, and current employees for changes in regulations or internal processes
- Updated patient files in EPIC database system with 100% accuracy and reviewed peer notes to ensure completeness
- Converted hardcopy patient files to EMR and trained staff on how to utilize new information